https://www.winability.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy of WinAbility Software Corporation
We respect your right to privacy. Any information gathered by WinAbility Software Corporation will be kept strictly confidential and will only be used or shared in ways for which you have specifically consented. Unless we have your express consent, we will not sell, rent or trade your personal information to any third party. We will take special care to protect the privacy and security of your information.
Because we feel your privacy is so important, we are providing this page to describe when and how we collect and use such information. This Privacy Policy covers the information you provide to us offline and at our web sites (www.winability.com, www.winability.us, www.winability.net, www.winability-software.com, and other such web sites of ours). Our Privacy Policy does not apply to third party web sites that may be accessible through our web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those third parties to learn how they collect and use information about you.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
WinAbility Software Corporation collects your personal information when you:
Purchase a product that we offer for sale
Our web site collects information about your billing and shipping addresses, email address, telephone number, as well as other information necessary to perform the transaction, such as the credit card information. We use such information to process your order and deliver the goods you have purchased to you, to determine whether you are exempt from the sales tax, and to confirm the validity of your order. It may also be stored in a cookie, on your computer (see below). We may use your email address to send you the order confirmation notices. We may also use your email address and telephone number to contact you to verify the information you have provided us with, for both your and our protection against credit card fraud. We may also use your email address to notify you of the availability of a product update, unless you opt-out of such notices. We will not use your email address to send you any other messages that you have not requested. We will not use your telephone number to call you for any other reason. We will not share any of your personal information with any third party, unless we are required to do so by law, or we have your express consent to do so. However, we reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. We may release certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.
Subscribe to receive a newsletter or update notices
If you opt-in to receive our email newsletters and/or the notifications about the new releases of our products, we will use your email address to send you the
materials you’ve subscribed to.
We will not use your email address to send you any other messages that you have not requested, nor will we share your email address with any third party, unless we are required to do so by law, or we have your express consent to do so.
Request customer support, check your license for validity, check for available software updates, report an error with our software, or use links or commands in our software to visit our web sites
Our web sites may collect your name, email address, the order number that you have previously placed with us, any comments you may enter into the contact form, the registered name on your current license for our software, the number of copies included in the license, the license key, the name and version information of the product of ours that you are using, the general technical information about the operating system and the web browser that you use, the network name and/or IP address of your computer, as well as other technical data that is normally used in the Internet connections. We may use such information to determine your eligibility to receive customer support and product upgrades, to check the validity of your current license to use our software, and to improve the quality of our products and web sites. It may also be stored in a cookie, on your computer (see below).
Collection and Use of Anonymous and Technical Information
Our web sites collect general usage information about visitors coming to our web and FTP sites. This information (sometimes referred to as "non-personally identifiable information") may include the address of the web site that you came from before visiting our site, which pages you visit on our site, which browser you used to view our site, and other similar technical information. This technical data is aggregated and used to measure and improve the effectiveness of our web sites. It may also be stored in a cookie, on your computer (see below).
Comments to web pages
When visitors leave comments on the web site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture may be visible to the public in the context of your comment.
How We Use Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data file that a web site may send to your web browser and that your browser may then store on your computer. We may use cookies to "remember" your previous visits to our web sites and information that you have previously entered into the forms, which would allow you to visit our web site without reentering such information over and over again. The cookies may also be used to keep track of what you have selected to purchase as you click through our site. We may also use cookies to allow you to access areas of our web site that are limited to registered users. We may also use the web site analytics software (such as Google Analytics) that may store the analytics information in its own cookies.
We do NOT allow other companies (third parties) to set cookies via our web sites.
Most web browsers allow you to automatically or selectively accept or reject cookies, by adjusting the preferences in your browser.
If you turn cookies off, there may be some features of our site that will not be available to you and some web pages may not display properly.
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
How long we retain your data
If you place an order for our products, order information and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can verify your license to use our software, and verify your eligibility to receive technical support or discounted upgrades. We do NOT store the full credit card number on our web server(s) beyond the time period that is technically necessary to process the credit card charge.
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Information storage, processing, and release
We use a variety of safeguards to protect your information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. For example, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology supporting strong encryption to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing any personal information transmitted to or from our Online Store. We only provide access to your personal information to our employees and other authorized parties on a "need to know" basis. If we store your personal information offline, we use strong encryption (at least 128-bit) to protect your data from misuse by unauthorized parties.
Information that is collected by or sent to us may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which we or our affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents maintain facilities. We may disclose this information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us or the site; (b) protect or defend the rights or property of WinAbility Software Corporation and its family of websites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our employees, users of our software or services, or members of the public.
WinAbility Software Corporation occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on its behalf, such as providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of reports. We will provide these companies only the information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.
You Are In Control Of Your Information
We will NOT use or share the personal information we collect in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information without first obtaining your consent (opt-in). If you do opt-in to receive communications from us, you can opt-out at any time. All e-mail communications from us, such as newsletters, tell you how to stop receiving them.
We want your information and preferences to be accurate and complete. If you would like to access or update the personal information we maintain about you in our systems, please call +1(435)200-5772 or contact us via the web form. You can also write us at:
WinAbility Software Corporation
P.O.BOX 75
LA VERKIN, UT 84745-0075
U.S.A.
You may use the same contact information above to send us a request that we delete personally identifiable information stored in the databases we actively use for research and daily business activities and other readily searchable media. Unless restricted by law, we will take all reasonable steps to functionally delete such information from our database(s). We will respond to your request to access, update or delete your information within five business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details (in a secure manner) to help us to respond to your request.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
If there are changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will only use your personal information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information, unless you later give your express consent for us to do otherwise.
Last revision date: May 24, 2018
Any questions?
Please contact us if you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy.
Useful Windows utilities, security and encryption software
Folder Guard
Password-protect and hide personal files and folders with Folder Guard for Windows 10, 8, 7, and XP. Read more...
USBCrypt
Encrypt and password-protect flash drives, external and internal USB and other drives with USBCrypt software for Windows 10, 8, 7,
and XP. Read more...
AB Commander
Take control of your files and folders with AB Commander file manager for Windows 10, 8, 7, Vista, and XP.
Read more...
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)
